Ending
We
We are Ojamama Oma!
This time we all want to play the NG word game!
Yay!
It's been a year since our debut, so I'm sure we all know each other's habits and what we're into these days,
I think I'm getting to know a lot of things now.
I know!
I think I understand!
It's been a year!
On the paper handed out to you, write down words that you think the person sitting to your right is likely to say, or that you think he/she is likely to make you say!
The key is to write it without the person next to you seeing it!
Did you all get it?
I did!
Did you write it, Miku?
Yes!
Give it to the person on your right and write it up when you receive it!
Then, please do it!
Oh, is that what you mean?
That's right!
Yes!
You're so mean!
You say it so much!
People seem to say this a lot!
That word you put on your forehead is the NG word!
So, you should anticipate the word and try not to say it, while those around you try to make you say it!
The person who says the NG word will be asked to say something cute and mocking to the camera!
The theme of the talk will be the year in review!
Let's go! Let the game begin!
Kira, you're in charge!
Me?
Yes, Kira!
Okay, everyone...
Yeah!Yeah!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Bye!
Just a quick, cute word.
Here you go!
I love you!
Oh!
It took six seconds.
There it is!
I know!
So, looking back over the past year.
I've been working hard on a lot of things.
But I'm happy for myself.
I'm happy.
The bond between the 10 of us has grown stronger.
You've been so careful.
I feel it keenly when I'm at the table.
I'm so glad that we've worked so hard together
We've worked so hard forever.
You used a word I don't use.
What about you, personally?
Personally.
Not if it's not.
You've been through a lot, right?
You're right.
You were a beginner.
A beginner.
And that...
You know what?
I live in Ishikawa.
Yes!
Wow!
Wait a minute!
Yes!
I think it's hard to write this.I think it's hard to write this.
It's hard to make you say too much.
I thought I was aiming too hard.
I was.
I thought you were right.
It's my own idea.
I'm so sure.
I wondered if you were sure.
It was Ishikawa.
Wow!
Everyone's so good!
Then your stupid head is cute!
Let's go for the idiot's head!
Please come visit us in Ishikawa sometime!
Thank you very much.
But you know what?
Ishikawa Prefecture on the 15th.
I'll be at the insti-densa
I'll be out shortly.
Congratulations.
Congratulations!
I also write once
Let's write.
Yes, I will.
Kanamin, a little from before
Kanamin.
That's right.
How was it?
This is different.
Well...
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Aah!
That was fun.
Wow!Wow!
That's crazy.
Me.
Oh, I might have a guess.
Oh, you can't?
No, no, no, I won't say it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I won't tell you.
I can't be.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
No?
That's great.
No, it's not.
I'm sorry.
What about you and Nico?
I'm...
I'm a tea drinker.
I've...
I've overcome a lot of obstacles.
It's been a great year.
Oh!
Noko, are you talking about this?
I'm going to say it.
Maybe it's that.
You're like a normal person.
That's why.
It's good that you brought someone younger.
I think we're all pretty much the same.
Oh, hey, you're a bit of a jerk.
Wait, no, no, no, no.
But he's cute.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
You're cute.
It's cute.Hmmm...
The best?
The best.
Best what?
Say it.
Cutest!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Did you say it? Did you say it?
I don't know.
You should talk to him more like a double.
It doesn't really matter.
Regardless.
Well, then...
I'm the cutest, right?
Yes!
What?
Huh?
You're cute.
Did you say it doesn't matter?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's awkward.
Nana-chan.
Cute Nana-chan!
I'm the cutest, right?
I love you!
You're so cute!
How's it going with the tepid ones?
You're talking to me like I'm a baby.
It's so sudden.
What?
You talked a lot.
I cut my bangs.
Oh!
So you're moving on... that's how I feel right now.
What? It's great.What? The best.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
How's it going? How are you?
I'm happy.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You're right, I probably wouldn't say that.
You're right.
I don't think I've ever heard you say it.
I think you've forgotten.
Talk about it twice a year.
Oh, I see.
It's really been a year, hasn't it?
It really flew by.
I've been trying so hard to tell you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah, sure.
You know what?
I have something to say.
Oh?
Yes, ma'am.
I want to say something.
About a year ago...
You said you wanted to marry me.
What?
But...
Lately...
He's been cheating on me.
In a year?
Yeah, in the last year.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You're right next to me.
Kitahara-san.
So...
I'd like to know why.
I'd like to hear it.I need to hear it.
The reason?
It's sad.
I've been number one for so long.
Suddenly I'm number two.
That sucks.
You know what?
Vita, that's terrible.
The tea drinker.
At the fan club event.
I was behind Momo.
I was there.
She had such beautiful bare feet.
You've changed just because of her legs?
Not exactly.
It's just... it's so easy.
Right?
Hey!
It's true.
Hey, guys.
It's love.
Mikkun said it the other day.
You're...
You're always second.
That's how it is.
You're better.
You're the best.
I love you.
What's my hand?
I don't know.
Shall we watch?
I think it's time.
Yes, sir.
Ready?
Aaaaah!
It's so...Oh, my God.
That's what you did?
We did it, didn't we?
It was fun, wasn't it?
First round
The folk theme is our goal for the second year.
Let's write accordingly.
The more we do it, the better.
Did it go well?
Yes, I did.
Then let's put it up at the top.
Ui.
That's good.
On your head.
That's so good.
Oh!
Let's go.
Let's go!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a little early.
I'll have a cup of tea.
I'd like to do a one-for-seventy-seven tour.
This is exactly where the members come from.
First scene.
I want to go around like we did in
I want to go around.
Everyone wants to go to their hometowns, don't they?
I want to go.
Of course we want to go.
That's why.
It was hot, right?
It was hot.
I'd have heat stroke, too.
It was really hot.
Where were you?Where is it?
I know exactly where.
Me too.
I want to go to Saga.
I'd like to go to Hokkaido.
I haven't been to Hokkaido recently.
I want to go to Hokkaido, too.
And I want to go to Tokyo.
Where's that?
Tokyo.
I'd love to go.
I've never been.
Where would you like to go?
Shikoku.
Wow, I know.
I've never been to Shikoku.
Maybe the highlands.
What's this?
Let's go on the last day in the last round.
Gilliout.
Outoo.
On the Changsha Bottle team.
Are you okay?
I'm stuck.
I'd love to do some gigs at various places in the tea room.
All right.
That's fine.
You've been working hard.
I said, "What?
One word.
What?
I want to work harder on social networking in my second year.
I want to do my best.
I could go there.You can go there.
To a texas.
Sure.
Or like the highlands.
CockroachesCockroachesCockroaches
Cockroach-cockroach-cockroach.
What happened... suddenly...
Maybe it was a joke.
Ah...
What?
You're all making funny faces.
Kilograms?
Yeah, I know.
You're a pretty girl.
I don't think so.
Are you sure you didn't reach Yelie?
What?
Wait, does it hurt? It hurts.
It hurts.
Hurts, doesn't it?
Can I tell you how I feel?
I'm so nervous, but I don't know what to say.
This feeling.
It's so sudden.
I don't know how to feel.
What is this feeling?
He says he's nervous about Kanami.
For me?
Not about who?
I mean, how does it make you feel?
Because we're all chicken.
Chicken.
I thought the topic this time was goals.
The second year.
I want to do my best in the video industry.I'd like to do well in the video industry.
That's for sure.
I'm on Twitter.
I'm also on Instagram.
TikTok is also on YouTube.
Which is the best?
I do all of them.
But the one I watch the most is...
TikTok.
This day and age.
Generation Z
TikTok is making me famous
Kirari tens of thousands of times
Oh, my God.
What's that?
I danced to it.
What one?
What kind?
If it's a dream, it's a different one.
Rocco, did you talk to him?
Rocco's goal is to make it to the second year.
Like Mikku said.
We're all from different places.
I want to go to different places
I want to go to many places and perform live.
Where do you want to go the most?
From Rocco's point of view.
Rocco would like to go to Aomori prefecture.
Aomori?
Is that so?
Apples. I want to go eat apples.
I want to go to my hometown again.I want to go to my hometown one more time, loco's.
For sure.
Kubo and Nanami are from
I'm from Shiga Prefecture.
Shiga Prefecture.
I don't want you to make that mistake.
It's hard, isn't it?
I like it now.
Seino
Happy!
You want to be told what to do.
I want to be made to say it.
It's disgusting.
Is this the morning?
You don't say.
What was that?
What is it?
I don't know the answer.
So, should we try to figure it out?
But...
It's Asaru.
I won't say.
It's like, "What's that?
You won't tell me?
It's used to show me how I feel.
It's used to intimidate me.
Hey, hey, hey.
It was in my dream.
It was only for Akira, wasn't it?
I knew it so well.
I knew after the first TikTok.
It's hard to tell.
For certain people.I think it's not good to make certain people
I think it's the other way around if you make them say
I can go buy it.
I want to try this again.
I want to.
This is my second year.
But in the third year, I'll be able to talk more.
I might be able to do more in Chiquila.
I'll see you soon.
I hope I'll have a chance to do it again.
So long.
That's all for now.
Bye bye.
I know.
Bye bye bye.
Love you this year too, Nopu and Tea Mama!